[
    {
        "question": "A car depreciates by 11% each year. In 8 years, what is the value of the car of its original price? (in decimal form)",
        "answer": 0.3936,
        "func": "<power>(0.89, 8)=0.3936"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the population of a city increases by a percentage of 2% every year, how many times will the population increase in 31 years?",
        "answer": 1.8476,
        "func": "<power>(1.02, 31)=1.8476"
    },
    {
        "question": "A cube has a side length of 1.31 meters. What is the volume of the cube in cubic meters?",
        "answer": 2.2481,
        "func": "<power>(1.31, 3)=2.2481"
    },
    {
        "question": "a bacteria triples every hour, how many bacteria will there be in 24 hours?",
        "answer": 282429536481,
        "func": "<power>(3, 24)=282429536481"
    },
    {
        "question": "What the area of a 7.777 meter-long square?",
        "answer": 60.4817,
        "func": "<power>(7.777, 2)=60.4817"
    },
    {
        "question": "A car travels 0.384 miles and then travels 1.63 more miles. How far did the car travel in total?",
        "answer": 2.014,
        "func": "<add>(0.384, 1.63)=2.014"
    },
    {
        "question": "A marathon runner has completed 8.7832 miles so far. He has 5.3689 miles left to run. What is the total distance of the marathon?",
        "answer": 14.1521,
        "func": "<add>(8.7832, 5.3689)=14.1521"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company has 13,289 employees and plans to hire 7,899 more. How many employees will the company have in total?",
        "answer": 21188,
        "func": "<add>(13289, 7899)=21188"
    },
    {
        "question": "This week, Mary earns 17.83 dollars on Monday, 18.99 dollars on Tuesday, 23.45 dollars on Wednesday, 14.12 dollars on Thursday, and 8.22 dollars on Friday. How much money did Mary earn this week?",
        "answer": 82.61,
        "func": "<add>(17.83, 18.99, 23.45, 14.12, 8.22)=82.61"
    },
    {
        "question": " The cost of an estate is 19,543,778.4 dollars. If the furnishings will cost at least 632,361 dollars, what is the minimum amount of money needed to buy the estate and furnish it?",
        "answer": 20176139.4,
        "func": "<add>(19543778.4, 632361)=20176139.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "The gas tank of car can hold up to 11.28 gallons of gas. Currently, a car only has 1.89 gallons of gas in its tank. How many more gallons of gas can the car hold if the driver wants to fill the tank?",
        "answer": 9.39,
        "func": "<subtract>(11.28, 1.89)=9.39"
    },
    {
        "question": "If a recipe calls for 892 cups of flour and you only have 134 cups, how many cups of flour do you need to buy?",
        "answer": 758,
        "func": "<subtract>(892, 134)=758"
    },
    {
        "question": "A runner has completed 8.9832 miles out of a 29.47-mile marathon. How many miles does the runner have left to run?",
        "answer": 20.4868,
        "func": "<subtract>(29.47, 8.9832)=20.4868"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company had 18,778 employees last year. This year, the company has 13,289 employees. How many employees did the company lose?",
        "answer": 5489,
        "func": "<subtract>(18778, 13289)=5489"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company has a budget of $1028137.23. They spent $79952.88 on office expenses. How much money is left?",
        "answer": 948184.35,
        "func": "<subtract>(1028137.23, 79952.88)=948184.35"
    },    
    {
        "question": " A reader is reading a really long book. She reads 67 pages per day, and it takes her 253 days to finish the book. How many pages are in the book at most?",
        "answer": 16951,
        "func": "<multiply>(67, 253)=16951"
    },
    {
        "question": "If there is a gemstone that costs only $0.37 a gram and Jack wants to buy 48,172.7 grams, how much would he need to spend?",
        "answer": 17823.899,
        "func": "<multiply>(0.37, 48172.7)=17823.899"
    },
    {
        "question": " A swimming pool has a length of 0.848 kilometers, and a width of 0.3766 kilometers. What is the area of the swimming pool in square kilometers?",
        "answer": 0.3193568,
        "func": "<multiply>(0.848, 0.3766)=0.3193568"
    },
    {
        "question": "If a car travels 0.384 miles in 1 minute, how many miles will it travel in 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 18.816,
        "func": "<multiply>(0.384, 49)=18.816"
    },
    {
        "question": "If a pizza has a diameter of 0.6273 inches, what is its circumference? (take pi to be 3.14159)",
        "answer": 1.970719407,
        "func": "<multiply>(0.6273, 3.14159)=1.970719407"
    },
    {
        "question": "If 327.87 ounces of sugar are required to make 52 cookies, how many ounces of sugar are required to make each cookie?",
        "answer": 6.3051,
        "func": "<divide>(327.87, 52)=6.3051"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company has a total budget of 21412879.32 dollars and wants to evenly distribute the money to 8889 employees. How much money will each employee get?",
        "answer": 2408.9188,
        "func": "<divide>(21412879.32, 8889)=2408.9188"
    },
    {
        "question": "A store sells a total of 898.75 ounces of cereal. If they sell 43 boxes of cereal, how many ounces of cereal are in each box?",
        "answer": 20.9012,
        "func": "<divide>(898.75, 43)=20.9012"
    },
    {
        "question": "A swimming pool has a volume of 19,338.74 gallons. If the water can evenly fill 532 buckets, how many gallons of water are in each bucket?",
        "answer": 36.351,
        "func": "<divide>(19338.74, 532)=36.351"
    },
    {
        "question": "A marathon is 26.2823 miles long. If a runner finishes the marathon in 216.3 minutes, what is the runner's average speed per mile?",
        "answer": 8.2299,
        "func": "<divide>(216.3, 26.2823)=8.2299"
    },
    {
        "question": "A construction company has three trucks that can transport a load in 23, 33, and 42 hours respectively. If the three trucks start transporting at the same time and repeatedly transport the load with no rest, how long will it take for them to finish transporting the load at the same time?",
        "answer": 10626,
        "func": "<lcm>(23, 33, 42)=10626"
    },
    {
        "question": "Two cyclists are riding on a circular track. The first cyclist completes a lap in 783 seconds, and the second cyclist completes a lap in 684 minutes. If they both start at the same time, how long will it take for them to meet at the starting point again?",
        "answer": 59508,
        "func": "<lcm>(783, 684)=59508"
    },
    {
        "question": "A teacher wants to give three different assignments. Assignment A cycles every 38 days, and Assignment B cycles every 49 days, and Assignment C cycles every 28 days. If the teacher gives all three assignments on the same day, how many days will it take for the teacher to give all three assignments on the same day again?",
        "answer": 3724,
        "func": "<lcm>(38, 49, 17)=3724"
    },
    {
        "question": "Two libaians have different reading habits. The first libaian reads a book every 289 days, and the second libaian every 272 days. If they both start reading a book on the same day, how many days will it take for them to start reading a book on the same day again?",
        "answer": 4624,
        "func": "<lcm>(289, 272)=4624"
    },
    {
        "question": "A factory has two machines. Machine A takes 182 minutes to produce a product, and Machine B takes 273 minutes to produce a product. If the factory starts both machines at the same time, what is the least amount of time it will take for both machines to produce a product at the same time?",
        "answer": "546",
        "func": "<lcm>(182, 273)=546"
    },
    {
        "question": "A cake is to be cut into square pieces. The cake is 259 mm long and 185 mm wide. What is the maximum possible length of a side of each piece?",
        "answer": 37,
        "func": "<gcd>(259, 185)=37"
    },
    {
        "question": "A bakery wants to package 66 cupcakes, 34 muffins, 54 cookies, and 32 brownies into boxes with the same number of baked goods in each box. What is the largest number of each type of baked good that can be in each box?",
        "answer": 2,
        "func": "<gcd>(66, 34, 54, 32)=2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary wants to distribute 144 chocolates, 126 lollipops, and 108 gummy bears into bags with the same number of candies in each bag. What is the largest number of each type of candy that can be in each bag?",
        "answer": 18,
        "func": "<gcd>(144, 126, 112)=18"
    },
    {
        "question": " A school has 6644 boys, 7248 girls, and also 906 non-binary students. If the school wants to divide the students into groups where each group has the same number of students and each group has only one type of student, what is the largest number of students that can be in each group?",
        "answer": 302,
        "func": "<gcd>(6644,7248,906)=302"
    },
    {
        "question": "A teacher is trying to equally distribute 896 pencils and 672 pens, and 1456 erasers to students. What is the largest number of students that can receive the same number of each type of school supply?",
        "answer": 112,
        "func": "<gcd>(896, 672, 1456)=112"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company has 45 employees and needs to form a committee of 7 members. How many ways can the company form the committee?",
        "answer": 45379620,
        "func": "<choose>(45, 7)=45379620"
    },
    {
        "question": "A classroom has 28 students and the teacher wants to choose a group of 19 students for a project. How many ways can the teacher form the group?",
        "answer": 6906900,
        "func": "<choose>(28, 19)=6906900"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ways can you form a team of 5 players from a reallt large squad of 101 players?",
        "answer": 79208745,
        "func": "<choose>(101, 5)=79208745"
    },
    {
        "question": "In a store, there are 197 different colors of shirts, but a customer can only buy 3 shirts. How many different ways can a customer choose shirts?",
        "answer": 1254890,
        "func": "<choose>(197, 3)=1254890"
    },
    {
        "question": "A pizza place offers 13 toppings. If a customer can choose 9 toppings for their pizza, how many different pizzas can they create?",
        "answer": 715,
        "func": "<choose>(13, 9)=715"
    },
    {
        "question": "A music festival has 23 bands performing. In how many ways can the organizers arrange the schedule for 7 bands to perform?",
        "answer": 1235591280,
        "func": "<permutate>(23, 7)=1235591280"
    },
    {
        "question": "A committee of 17 people needs to be formed from a group of 8 candidates. Each committee member can only be assigned to one position. How many ways can the committee be formed?",
        "answer": 980179200,
        "func": "<permutate>(17,8)=980179200"
    },
    {
        "question": " A group of 14 students are going to take a photo in a row. In how many ways can the students arrange themselves in a row?",
        "answer": 87178291200,
        "func": "<permutate>(14, 14)=87178291200"
    },
    {
        "question": "A teacher needs to select 4 students from a class of 76 students to make presentations. If we consider the presentation order, how many ways can the teacher arrange the presentation order?",
        "answer": 30791400,
        "func": "<permutate>(76,4)=30791400"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many different ways can you arrange the letters in the 7-letter word \"UCSDABC\"?",
        "answer": 5040,
        "func": "<permutate>(7,7)=5040"
    },
    {
        "question": " A sqaure swimming pool has an area of 7876.56 square meters. What is the length of one side of the pool?",
        "answer": 88.7468,
        "func": "<sqrt>(7876.56)=88.7468"

    },
    {
        "question": " The variance of a set of data is 0.0284. What is the standard deviation of the data?",
        "answer": 0.1685,
        "func": "<sqrt>(0.0284)=0.1685"
    },
    {
        "question": "x is a positive integer. If x^2 = 789789, what is the value of x?",
        "answer": 888.7007,
        "func": "<sqrt>(789789)=888.7007"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the value of √1.056?",
        "answer": 1.0276,
        "func": "<sqrt>(1.056)=1.0276"
    },
    {
        "question": "Given the equation: 10^x = 123.2, what is the value of x?",
        "answer": 2.0906,
        "func": "<log>(123.2)=2.0906"
    },
    {
        "question": "A solution has a hydrogen ion [H+] concentration of 0.00008342 M. What is the pH of the solution?",
        "answer": 4.0787,
        "func": "-<log>(0.00008342)=4.0787"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the result of log(0.000324).",
        "answer": -3.4881,
        "func": "<log>(0.000325)=-3.4881"
    },
    {
        "question": "A certain radioactive substance decays naturally such that every hour, the quantity is reduced by a factor of e. If we start with a certain quantity Q, how long will it take for the quantity to halve?",
        "answer": 0.6931,
        "func": "-<ln>(0.5)=0.6931"
    },
    {
        "question": " If we know e^x equals 3788.444, what is the value of x?",
        "answer": 8.2397,
        "func": "<ln>(3788.444)=8.2397"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of ln(686868)?",
        "answer": 13.4399,
        "func": "<ln>(686868)=13.4399"
    },
    {
        "question": "A farmer wants to divide 7893 pounds of apples evenly among 777 baskets. If each basket must have the same weight of apples, what is the remainder when the apples are divided?",
        "answer": 123,
        "func": "<remainder>(7893, 777)=123"
    },
    {
        "question": "A farmer has 1899 eggs and wants to put them in cartons of 18 eggs each. How many eggs will be left over after he fills as many complete cartons as possible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "func": "<remainder>(1899, 24)=3"
    },
    {
        "question": "A store has 854 pencils and wants to put them into 123-packs. How many pencils will be left over?",
        "answer": 116,
        "func": "<remainder>(854, 123)=116"
    },
    {
        "question": " There are a total of 11241241 bacteria in a petri dish. If the bacteria should be separated into 234 other petri dishes, how many bacteria will be left over in the original petri dish?",
        "answer": 115,
        "func": "<remainder>(11241241, 234)=115"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenny withdraw $12,345 from her bank account, and she wants to buy as many $33 jellycat teddy bears as possible, and use the rest of the money to buy her a meal. How much money will she have for her meal?",
        "answer": 3,
        "func": "<remainder>(12345, 33)=3"
    }
] 